https://www.thinkfun.com/privacy/

|
Worldwide
ThinkFun Privacy Statement
This privacy policy describes how ThinkFun Inc. (“ThinkFun”) handles information received from users of the ThinkFun.com website.
Information Collection
The majority of products and services on our site are offered without collecting any personally identifiable information from you. You can surf our site and view much of our content anonymously.
Information You Provide
We collect information when you provide it to us, such as by contacting us or by joining one of our mailing lists.
Information Collected from You with Technology
Through this site, we also automatically collect some non-personally identifiable information about you using technology. For instance, we may collect the domain from which you access the Internet; IP address; browser type; screen resolution; Internet connection speed; operating system; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked to our site. ThinkFun uses such information to make our site more interesting and useful to you. We normally don’t combine this type of information with personally identifiable information; however, we will combine this information with personally identifiable information in some cases, such as to enforce compliance with our house rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site or other people.
How We Use Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that a website sends to your computer while you are viewing the website. These pieces of information allow the website to remember important information that will make your use of that site more useful. This website, like other Internet sites, uses cookies for a variety of purposes. You can usually set your Internet browser to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to turn off all cookies. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn about the options your browser provides regarding cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to site features that make your Web experience more efficient — like the features mentioned above — and some of our services will not function properly.
How We Use the Information
We use personally identifiable information in a limited number of ways. We use the information to operate our business, to respond to your requests and to provide information or updates from ThinkFun (depending on the option you have chosen). We may use the information we collect to understand and improve our website, our products and our services.  In addition, we may also use the information to contact you regarding changes to our privacy policy or other policies that may affect you and your use of our website, products and services.
How We Share the Information
We will only share your information as described in this policy or with your consent.
Companies That Are Standing in for ThinkFun.com
We may use the services of agents and contractors to assist us in providing our products and services, such as contractors that assist us in operating the website. In those instances, we need to share your information with them. These companies are basically standing in for ThinkFun, and they are not allowed to use the information for independent purposes.
Legal Requirements and Organizations That Help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Guests and Our Site
We will give out personal information as required by law, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena; to enforce our Terms of Use or our site or game rules; or to protect the safety and security of visitors or our site.
Transfer of Assets
We may transfer information about you if we sell all or a portion of our assets, such as if we are acquired by or merged with another entity.
Your Choices
You can use most aspects of our site without giving us any personally identifiable information. When you do register with us or give us personally identifiable information, you will have an opportunity to limit e-mail communications from ThinkFun. You can also request at any time that we not send future marketing e-mail to you either by unsubscribing using the instructions in our emails or by contacting us at support@ThinkFun.com. Also, as mentioned above, you may be able to use your browser controls to limit the information that we collect through cookies.
Security
Maintaining the security of our visitors’ personally identifiable information is important to us. ThinkFun takes reasonable technical, contractual, administrative and physical security steps to protect visitors’ information. Personally identifiable information that we collect is stored on our secure server and can only be accessed by certain employees within our company. When you provide credit card information we use a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) Certificate to encrypt and protect your credit card data. We show the Norton Secured seal on our website to assure our visitors of these security practices. Click here to learn more about this seal.
Accessing and Changing Information
You can access or change the personally identifiable information you have provided to us by logging into your account on the website, using your email address and password you used during the initial set-up. If you forget your password, you can retrieve it using the security question that you set during registration.
Children’s Privacy
ThinkFun does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian believes that a child under 13 has provided ThinkFun with personally identifiable information, you can contact Customer Service by email at support@thinkfun.com to request deletion of the information. Please include information in the email that will help us identify the child’s account.
Links to Third-Party Sites
Our site may contain links to third-party sites. Their information practices may be different than ours, and we do not have control over the information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. You should consult the privacy policies of these other sites to learn about their practices.
Updates
From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy.  We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by updating this page.  We encourage you to periodically check back to learn what information we collect, how we use it and to whom we share it. Your continued use of our website after any such changes have been posted constitutes your agreement to those changes.
Contact Us
If you need further assistance, please contact us at support@ThinkFun.com,  703-549-4999, or write to us at:
ThinkFun Inc.
1321 Cameron Street
Alexandria, VA 22314
Legal Notice
This website is operated by
ThinkFun Inc.
1321 Cameron Street
Alexandria, VA 22314
USA
Federal Tax ID: 54-1297151
Any external links included on this website lie outside the operator’s responsibilities.
The content of external webpages is monitored for statutory violations before being included on the Thinkfun website. However, Thinkfun has no influence over the content of these webpages and takes no responsibility for them. Thinkfun carries out regular inspections of its links. If a statutory violation is brought to our attention, that link is deleted immediately. In the case of illegal, corrupt or incomplete material, as well as damages that may arise as a result of use or disuse of links, only the provider is liable.
We want to hear from you
Customer Feedback Survey
Microsites for our Games
Robot Turtles
Support
Contact Us
FAQ
International Customers
Subscribe For Updates
We use cookies to guarantee the best possible service for you. Continuing to surf this website means you consent to this use of cookies. You can find out more about our use of cookies in our privacy statement.Ok
